你的论点完全缺乏科学价值
Your argument is lacking in all scientific merit.
这很明确 超人通过飞入"黄日"核武器 清理他的衣服
It is well established superman cleans his uniform by flying into Earth's yellow sun,
由此能清除所有污染物
which incinerates any contaminate matter
从而留下安全的氪星布料 既无损坏又完全清洁
and leaves the invulnerable kryptonian fabric unharmed and daisy fresh.
要是他弄了点氪星的物质在上面呢
What if he gets something Kryptonian on it?
例如
Like what?
我不知道  氪星的芥末
I don't know. Kryptonian mustard.
我觉得我们完全能认为氪星爆炸时
I think we can safely assume that all Kryptonian condiments
已将所有氪星的调味品都摧毁了
were destroyed when the planet Krypton exploded.
又或者它变成了芥末氪星石
Or it turned into mustard Kryptonite,
唯一能摧毁 威胁地球的邪恶氪星热狗
the only way to destroy a rogue Kryptonian hotdog threatening Earth.
拉杰  拜托
Raj, please,
严肃点 超人的身体是氪星的 因此他的汗水也是氪星的
let's stay serious here. Superman's body is Kryptonian, therefore his sweat is Kryptonian.
对  要是沾到氪星汗渍呢
Yeah, what about Kryptonian pit stains?
超人在地球不会出汗
Superman doesn't sweat on Earth.
好啊 他应邀去肯朵的波特城赴晚餐
Okay, he's invited for dinner in the Bottle City of Kandor.
他把自己变小  进入该城 在那里  他失去了超能力
He miniaturizes himself, enters the city where he loses his superpowers. Now,
晚餐前  主人说 玩一会氪星绳球如何
before dinner, his host says, "Who's up for a little Kryptonian tetherball?"
超人说  可以啊  玩得大汗淋漓 回到地球
Superman says "Sure," works up a sweat, comes back to Earth,
他的衣服已经沾了无法去除的氪星汗渍
his uniform now stained with indestructible Kryptonian perspiration.
将死你
Boo ya.
超人能在离开波特前
Superman would have taken his uniform
把衣服放到肯朵的干洗机清洗
to a Kandorian dry cleaner before he left the Bottle.
肯朵的干洗机  我放弃
"Kandorian dry cl..." I give up.
你们完全没法跟这人理论
You can't have a rational argument with this man.
那不是去年赢得 麦克亚瑟天才奖的家伙吗
isn't that the guy who won the MacArthur genius grant last year?
不  别一次全部人看
No, not all at once.
那怎么看
Then how?
莱纳德先看
Leonard.
现在轮到拉杰
Now, Raj.
现在轮到谢尔顿
Now, Sheldon.
我没看清  能再看一遍吗
I didn't get a good look. Can I go again?
不行
No.
是戴维·安德希尔  那又怎么样
It's David Underhill. So what?
怎么样
So what?
他对高能正点子的观察报告
His observation of high-energy positrons
首次确切证明了
has provided the first conclusive evidence
银河暗物质的存在
for the existence of galactic dark matter.
我只给你两个词
I have two words for you.
一个是"太"  一个是"好了"
The first is "big," the other's "whoop."
确实是很好
It is a big whoop.
这几乎颠覆了
It made almost all the work
所有你在这里做的工作成果
you've done since you've been here completely useless.
-才怪  -才怪
Did not. Did, too.
才
Did...
好吧  有部分吧  但是
Okay, maybe  some of it, but...
这小子只是在天时地利的时候
Look, the guy was just in the right place,
利用范式方法重新解释了银河系
at the right time with the right paradigm-shifting
纯粹是狗屎运
reinterpretation of the universe. He got lucky.
不仅如此
In more ways than one.
他长得很帅呢
He's a very handsome man.
对我没什么影响  如果换成我
Doesn't do anything for me. If I was gonna go that way,
我会更像扎克·埃夫隆那种类型
I'm more of a Zac Ephron kinda guy.
对  要是你能有那么一点像他
Oh, yeah, like you have a shot with Zac Ephron.
打扰一下
Excuse me...
你是莱纳德·霍夫斯塔德吗
Are you Leonard Hofstadter?
是的
Uh... yeah.
我是戴维·安德希尔
I'm David Underhill.
好的
Uh... y-yeah.
盖博豪斯博士说
Yeah, Dr. Gablehauser said if I wanted
如果我要在光电倍增实验室准备试验
to set something up in the photomultiplier lab,
你能帮我忙
that you'd be able to give me a hand?
你要和我一起做实验
You want to work with me? Well,
你要是有时间的话  是的
if you have a little time, yeah.
哇  当然有
Wow.... Y-yeah, sure.
没问题
Yeah, no problem. Uh...
这是我的住宅电话
Here's my home number.
我的手机号码
Here's my cell.
办公室电话
Here's my office.
还有住在新泽西的父母家的电话
Here's my parents' number up in New Jersey.
他们总能找到我
They always know how to reach me. So... Okay.
对了  恭喜你获得麦克亚瑟天才奖  我很崇拜你
Congratulations on the MacArthur Grant, by the way. Big fan.
谢谢  我会打电话给你
Thanks. I'll call you.
好的
Okay.
拜拜
Bye-bye!
看什么看
What are you looking at?
没见过伪君子啊
You've never seen a hypocrite before?
《生活大爆炸》
第二季  第11集
遥遥落后  沃罗威茨需要投出全倒
Trailing badly, Wolowitz needs a strike
才有希望追上谢尔顿·库珀
if he has any hopes of catching up with Sheldon Cooper,
他在第九个计分格时占尽优势 最高记录68
who is dominating in the ninth frame with a career-best 68.
好啊  伙计们
Hey, guys!
那个不算
That doesn't count.
重来  重来
Do over! Do over!
Wii保龄球游戏里可是投球无回的
There are no do-overs in Wii bowling.
我的朋友做运动时总会有重来的
There are always do-overs when my people play sports.
有什么比Wii保龄球之夜 还重要的
Where were you that's more important than Wii bowling night?
其实  我
Actually, I was...
这是反问句 没什么能比 Wii保龄球之夜重要
It's a rhetorical question. There is nothing more important than Wii bowling night.
得了吧  不就是个电子游戏嘛
Come on, it's just a video game.
而且我们玩得很逊
And we suck at it.
很好的队长动员演说嘛
Nice motivational speech from the team captain.
你去哪了?
Where were you?
我去戴维·安德希尔那了
I was working with Dave Underhill.
哦 "戴维" 听起来莱纳德有了新的"好朋友"
Ooh, "Dave." Sounds like Leonard's got a new BFF.
事实上 他真的很酷
Actually, he's pretty cool.
不仅仅因为他是个天才
I mean, not only is he a brilliant scientist,
他还是个黑钻[户外运动品牌]滑雪高手
but it turns out he's a Black Diamond skier.
他收集老式摩托车 他还在一个摇滚乐队里演奏呢
He collects vintage motorcycles. He plays in a rock band.
怎样? 我们也是一个乐队啊
So? We're in a rock band.
不
No...
我们是在X-Box里面
We play Rock Band on our X-Box.
感谢主音吉他手激动人心的致辞
Nice motivational speech from our lead guitarist.
他还很幽默
He's funny, too.
他还绘声绘色的模仿了
He does this hysterical impersonation
史蒂芬·霍金的电话性爱
of Stephen Hawking having phone sex.
你穿着什么呢
What are you wearing?
还是他演得比较像
That's not... He does it better.
总之 他说明天他要带我去体育馆
Anyway, he said he was gonna take me to the gym tomorrow,
我先回屋练练仰卧起坐的
so I'm gonna go practice my situps.
排山倒海的男性吸引
Whoa. Humongous man crush, dude.
兄弟情的完美演绎
Yeah. It's officially a bro-mance.
嘿 谢尔顿 你和莱纳德要不要弄棵圣诞树?
Hey, Sheldon, are you and Leonard putting up a Christmas tree?
不 我们不庆祝
No, because we don't celebrate
古老的异教农神节
the ancient pagan festival of Saturnalia.
农神节?
Saturnalia?
孩子们 过来坐好了
Gather round, kids,
又到谢尔顿最爱的圣诞特别节目时间了
it's time for Sheldon's beloved Christmas special.
在基督教出现之前的那些岁月
In the pre-Christian era,
每当冬至来临大地枯萎
as the winter solstice approached and the plants died,
异教徒把常青的枝杈带回家中
pagans brought evergreen boughs into their homes
用这种形式来表示
as an act of sympathetic magic, intended
保护生命的本质直到春来再次到来
to guard the life essences of the plants until spring.
这种风俗后来
This custom was later appropriated
被北欧人继承  于是演变成了
by Northern Europeans and eventually it becomes
现在的圣诞树
the so-called Christmas tree.
那么查理·布朗  你看到什么叫做无聊了吧
And that, Charlie Brown, is what boredom is all about.
好吧 谢谢
Okay, well, thank you
不过我给你和莱纳德
for that, but I got you and Leonard
买了点蠢蠢的小礼物
a few silly neighbor gifts, so I'll just
我回头搁我的圣诞树底下好了
put them under my tree.
等等!
Wait!
你给我买了个礼物?
You bought me a present?
你干吗要这么做?
Why would you do such a thing?
不知道 因为是圣诞节?
I don't know. 'Cause it's Christmas?
哦 佩妮 我知道你认为自己很大方
Oh, Penny. I know you think you're being generous,
但送礼是建立在互利互惠的原则上的
but the foundation of gift-giving is reciprocity.
你还没给我礼物
You haven't given me a gift.
就已经塞给我一份责任
You've given me an obligation.
别难过 佩妮 这是新手常犯的错
Don't feel bad, Penny, it's a classic rookie mistake.
我和谢尔顿过的第一个犹太教光明节
My first Hanukkah with Sheldon,
他对我吼了八个晚上
he yelled at me for eight nights.
没关系 你不用送我什么东西以表回馈
Now, hey, it's okay.You don't have to get me anything in return.
当然要 这种风俗的精髓就是
Of course I do. The essence of the custom
现在我不得不出去给你买点东西
is that I now have to go out and purchase for you
价值相当的礼物
a gift of commensurate value
这礼物得体现对我们友谊的相同的感知价值
and representing the same perceived level of friendship
这种感知价值体现于你送我的礼物
as that represented by the gift you've given me.
知道今年自杀率是怎么直线上升的了吧
It's no wonder suicide rates skyrocket this time of year.
好吧  忘了这件事吧
Okay, you know what? Forget it.
我没有给你准备礼物
I'm not giving you a present.
太晚了  我都看到了  那个小精灵贴纸
No, it's too late. I see it. That elf sticker
上面写着  给谢尔顿
says, "To Sheldon."
木已成舟
The die has been cast.
冥冥有手写天书
[欧玛尔·海亚姆波斯诗人  此句曾被马丁·路德·金引用]
汉尼拔已经翻越了阿尔卑斯山
[迦太基名将汉尼拔曾率领军队及大象翻越积雪的阿尔卑斯山进入意大利]
我知道  有意思 特别是发生在别人身上
I know. It's funny when it's not happening to us.
谢尔顿  我非常非常抱歉
Sheldon, I am very, very sorry.
别  别  我自找的
No. No, I brought this on myself
谁让我不小心成为你生命中美好又重要的一部分呢
by being such an endearing and important part of your life.
谁开车带我去商场
I'm going to need a ride to the mall.
现在发生在咱们头上了
It's happening to us.
你还好吧
Are you gonna make it?
还好吧
Yeah, I guess.
好的
All right.
谢谢你让我开你的摩托
Thanks for letting me try out your motorcycle.
不客气
No problem.
我不知道它这么沉
I had no idea it was so heavy.
就这么压到我身上了是吧
The thing just fell right over on me, didn't it?
是啊  还没跑起来算你走运
Yeah. Lucky for you it wasn't moving.
-莱纳德您还好吧  -还好
-Oh, hey, Leonard. Ooh, are you okay? -Oh, yeah.
就是个摩托车小意外
It's just a little motorcycle accident.
我的天  你开得有多快
My God, how fast were you going?
不晓得  就在电光火石之间
I don't know. It's all such a blur.
很幽默  他连发动都发动不起来
Good one. He couldn't even get it started.
嗨  戴维
Hi. Dave. Hi.
佩妮  是你的摩托
Penny. So it's your motorcycle?
没摔坏吧
Is it okay?
没事
It's fine.
算那车走运
Lucky for the bike
有我的腿垫着
it landed on my leg.
你介意帮我搀这位机车选手一下么
You mind giving me a hand with speed racer here?
好的好的
Oh, yeah. Yeah, sure.
戴维你是怎么认识莱纳德的
So, um, Dave, how do you know Leonard?
我是个物理学家
I'm a physicist.
你才不是呢
No, you're not.
有什么奇怪的么
Why is that so surprising?
主要是我所认识的物理学家
Uh, well, it's just that the physicists I know
都又白又宅
are indoorsy and pale.
我不是宅男
I'm not indoorsy.
我的防晒霜很好用
I just wear the appropriate sun block
所以黑色素沉淀得很少
because I don't take melanoma lightly.
那你是
So, are you
在和莱纳德一起做实验么
and Leonard working on an experiment together?
事实上我们在
Yeah, actually we are.
我们在检测光电倍增管的
Yeah, we're examining the radiation levels
辐射强度
of photomultiplier tubes
用在一种新的暗物质探测器上面的
for a new dark matter detector.
亲爱的
Uh, sweetie, sweetie,
我在和戴维说话
Dave was talking.
你知道的  我爱好科学
You know, I love science.
-从什么时候开始的  -一直都是啊
-Since when? -Since always.
叫我科学怪人吧  我就是为
Call me a geek, but I am just nuts
这些亚原子痴迷不已
for the whole subatomic- particle thing.
我叫你什么也不会叫你科学怪人的
The last thing I would ever call you is a geek.
呵呵  我就是啊
Ha. Well, that's what I am--
怪才天后
queen of the nerds.
如果你愿意
Well, if you like,
我可以带你参观我们工作的实验室
I could show you the lab we're working in.
我们有一些很棒的玩意  激光器什么的
We've got some cool toys, you know-- lasers and stuff.
你知道么  我一直都想见识下真正的科学实验室
You know, I have always wanted to see a big science lab.
什么时候开始的
Since when?
一直都是呀
Since always.
莱纳德  你还好么
Leonard, are you okay here? Uh...
-还好吧  -我们现在就去如何
-Yeah. I guess. -How 'bout we go see it now?
之后我们可以到海边兜风
Maybe afterwards we take the bike up the coast,
再来点吃的东西
We grab a little bite to eat...
真不错
Um... Yeah. Yeah, that sounds great.
我去拿个外套
Let me just get my jacket.
她很可爱嘛
Boy, she'll do, huh?
是啊  如果你喜欢这个类型的
Yeah, if you like that type.
你和她
So, you and her...?
没关系  就是邻居
No, just neighbors.
真的
Really.
真难想象你就住她隔壁
I don't know how you live next door to that
居然没有什么行动
without doing something about it.
事实上
Actually...
科学就是我的爱人
science is my lady.
好吧  咱们走吧
Okay. Let's go.
好的
All right.
明天见  莱纳德
See you tomorrow, Leonard.
明天见  再见佩妮
See ya. 'Bye, Penny.
玩得开心
Have fun.
是谁
Yes?
你没带钥匙么
Did you forget your key?
我看这没有什么女人想要的
I don't see anything in here a woman would want.
开玩笑吧
You're kidding.
这里有身体乳液  沐浴精油  香皂
You've got lotions and bath oils and soaps.
简直是雌激素的帽子戏法[三连发]
that's the estrogen hat trick.
我看是山寨版发音的
What it is is a cacophonous assault
尤加利属植物  月桂树的果实  肉桂和香草
of eucalyptus, bayberry, cinnamon and vanilla.
就好像我的头卡到土耳其皇帝的睡衣里面一样
It's as if my head were trapped in the pajamas of a sultan.
谢尔顿  如果你不喜欢这些东西
Sheldon, if you don't like this stuff,
我们去隔壁给她做个填充玩具熊也行
let's just go next door and build her a bear.
告诉过你  我害怕熊
I told you before, bears are terrifying.
拜托
Come on,
沐浴用品  完美的选择
bath stuff. It's perfect!
这里有香氛蜡烛  洗面扑
You got a scented candle, a cleansing buff,
薄荷和绿茶味的沐浴精油  放松身心
spearmint and green tea scented bath oil, promotes relaxation.
前提假设是佩妮身心紧张
That presupposes Penny is tense.
她认识你  能不紧张么
She knows you. She's tense.
我们都紧张  买个礼品篮
We all are. Buy a basket!
您好  我们选好了
Excuse me, we're ready.
我们还没选好
No, we're not.
假设我同意
Let's say for a moment that I accept
沐浴礼品这个假设
the bath item gift hypothesis,
现在我要考考你了
I now lay the following conundrum at your feet:
我们该买多大的
Which size?
就这个  我们走
This one. Let's go.
你想都没想过
You put no thought into that.
不好意思  就这个
I'm sorry. Uh... this one.
我们走
Let's go!
我没有足够的数据进行分析
I have insufficient data to proceed.
不好意思小姐
Excuse me, miss?
什么事
Yes?
如果我送给你这个礼物篮
If I were to give you this gift basket,
根据这个行为本身  如果没有其他数据
based on that action alone and no other data,
请推断并描述我们之间的 假定关系
infer and describe the hypothetical relationship that exists between us.
不好意思
Excuse me?
这里
Here.
我们是朋友么
Now, are we friends?
同事还是情人
Colleagues? Lovers?
你是我的祖母么
Are you my grandmother?
我不明白你在说什么
I don't understand what you're talking about
不过你让我觉得有点不爽
and you're making me a little uncomfortable.
看到没  就像你和佩妮
See? Sounds just like you and Penny.
我们就要这个了
We'll take it.
莱纳德  过来一块儿坐
Hey, Leonard. Come, join us.
哦  嘿  戴维
Oh, hey, Dave.
还有佩妮  你也在这
And Penny, what a surprise.
嘿 莱纳德
Hey, Leonard.
戴维刚刚带我在校园里逛了逛
Dave was just showing me around the university.
你知道么 这个地方真是妙不可言
You know, this place is unbelievable!
我当然知道 这一年半我一直说要带你来看看
Yeah, I know. I've been offering to show you around for a year and a half.
你总是说你要去练瑜伽
You always said you had yoga.
从没说过
I never said that.
可能我听错了
Maybe I heard you wrong.
有很多词听起来像瑜伽
A lot of words sound like "yoga."
莱纳德 这真是一个很奇妙的女人
This is an amazing woman, Leonard.
她的思想敏捷而又有求知欲
She has a curious and agile mind,
更不用提她其他敏捷而奇特的方面了
not to mention being curious and agile in other respects.
别说了
Oh, shut up!
没错 闭嘴吧
Yes, please shut up.
那么  戴维
So, um, Dave,
我们是不是该回实验室干活了?
don't you think you and I should get back to the lab?
你知道 暗物质是不会去自己发现自己的
You know, that dark matter isn't going to detect itself.
我正想下午请个假
Actually, I was thinking about taking the afternoon off
然后和佩妮做个别的"实验"
so I could work on another experiment with Penny.
我们去做实验?
Really? We're going to do an experiment?
我们去试试龙舌兰酒
Uh-huh. We're going to explore the effects of tequila shots
在一个22岁尤物身上会有什么作用
on a gorgeous 22-year-old woman.
那不是实验
It's not an experiment!
再说你昨晚也见到会发生什么了
You saw what happened last night.
走么?  好
You ready to go? Yeah.
噢  我能骑摩托车吗
Oh, can I drive the motorcycle?
可以啊  有什么不行的
Yeah, why not?
你肯定不会比莱纳德开得还糟的
You can't do any worse than Leonard.
真有趣啊
That's funny.
顺便说一句  我的腿疼死了
By the way, my leg is killing me.
谢谢关心
Thanks for asking.
大新闻  莱纳德
Mmm, great news, Leonard.
我已经解决了送佩妮礼物的两难困境了
I've solved my Penny gift dilemma.
我好高兴哦
Yippee.
你想啊  我可能会送得过于好或过于寒碜
You see, the danger was that I might under or over-reciprocate,
但我已经想出了一个很简单的点子
but I have devised a foolproof plan.
我会先打开她给我的礼物
See, I will open her gift to me first
接着借故离开
and then excuse myself,
假装消化不良
feigning digestive distress.
然后我会上网查她送的礼物的价格
Then I'll look up the price of her gift online,
从篮子里选一样价格最接近的东西 送给她
choose the basket closest to that value, give it to her
最后我把剩下来的以全价退回去
and then I'll return the others for a full refund.
真聪明啊
Brilliant.
的确如此
It is, isn't it?
我可以把这些东西藏在你房间里吗
Is it okay if I hide them in your room?
这气味让我想吐
The smell makes me nauseated.
随便你怎么弄啦
Do whatever you want.
谢谢  你真是太高尚了
Thank you, that's very gracious.
先生们
Gentlemen.
你为什么不做莱纳德才做的事情
Why couldn't you have just done what Leonard did
给佩妮介绍个男朋友
and get Penny a new boyfriend?
我的腿疼死了
My leg is killing me.
谢谢关心
Thanks for asking.
我只有一个问题想问你
Okay, I have just one question for you.
当我很开心的和你在一起的时候
While I am perfectly happy with the way things are between us,
你说你不想和我约会
you said that you didn't want
只是因为我对你来说太聪明了
to go out with me because I was too smart for you!
那好吧  新闻来了  女士
Well, news flash, lady
戴维·安德希尔比我聪明十倍
David Underhill is ten times smarter than me!
对我来说  你得把一个道钉钉进
You'd have to drive a railroad spike into his brain
他脑子里  我才能在国际跳棋中打败他
for me to beat him at checkers!
和他相比
Next to him,
我比较像那些打手语的大猩猩之一
I'm like one of those sign-language gorillas
只知道怎么要葡萄
who knows how to ask for grapes!
所以  我的问题是...
So, my question is...
我聪明又怎么了啊
What's up with that?!
你干嘛对我大吼大叫啊
Why are you yelling at me?
对不起  对不起  对不起
Sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry!
别介意  我们没事了
Never mind, we're cool.
戴维并没有你聪明
Dave is not smarter than you.
他是个白痴
He's an idiot.
真的吗  你为什么这么说啊
Really? Why would you say that?
因为聪明的人会把他老婆的裸照从手机里删了
Because a smart guy takes the nude photos of his wife
在他打算把他女朋友的裸照 存进手机之前
off his cell phone before he tries to take nude photos of his girlfriend.
他打算给你拍裸照吗
He tried to take nude photos of you?
你就听到了这个
That's what you took from that?!
这家伙已经结婚了
The guy is married!
噢  是的
Oh, yeah.
对不起  那真是太糟糕了
I'm so-- Oh, that's terrible.
而你  如果你和我约会的时候
And you, if you are so okay
是很开心的
with the way things are between us,
你干嘛这么嫉妒啊
why are you so jealous?
恩...
Well, uh...
重要的是他已经结婚了  而且这太糟糕了
The important thing is he's married and that's terrible!
球救得好啊  天才啊
Nice save, genius.
蛋酒要吗
Eggnog?
我不能吃乳糖
Lactose.
里面只有朗姆酒
It's just rum.
在半小时前里面就已经不是蛋酒了
It stopped being eggnog like half an hour ago.
很好喝啊
Smooth.
比你更味美啊
Smoother than you.
拜托  现在是圣诞节  就这么对我啊
Come on, it's Christmas, just give me this one.
好吧  圣诞快乐
Okay, Merry Christmas.
顺便提一句  我的腿疼死了
By the way, my leg is killing me.
谢谢关心
Thanks for asking.
-圣诞快乐  -圣诞快乐
- Merry Christmas. - Merry Christmas.
你的腿怎么样了
How's your leg?
很好  谢谢关心  进来吧
Very good, thanks for asking. Come on in.
哦  真棒  佩妮  你来和我交换礼物了
Ah, good, Penny, you're here to exchange gifts.
当你知道无论你送什么
You'll be pleased to know
我都有相应的准备着  你会很高兴的
I'm prepared for whatever you have to offer.
好的  给你
Okay, here.
我要声明一下  我现在有些消化不良
I should note I'm having some digestive distress,
所以  如果我突然离开一下  不要惊异哦
so, if I excuse myself abruptly, don't be alarmed.
噢  一条餐巾
Oh, a napkin.
把它翻过来
Turn it over.
送给谢尔顿
"To Sheldon,
多福多寿
"live long and prosper.
莱纳德·尼莫哀致[《星际迷航》中演员]
Leonard Nimoy."
是的  他来饭馆
Yeah, he came into the restaurant.
很抱歉餐巾脏了  他用它擦过嘴了
Sorry the napkin's dirty. He wiped his mouth with it.
我有莱纳德·尼莫哀的DNA了
I possess the DNA of Leonard Nimoy?!
对啊...
Well...
是  是的  我想是这样的
Yeah, yeah. I guess.
但是  看哪  他还在上面签名了
But look, he signed it.
你难道没有意识到这意味着什么吗
Do you realize what this means?!
我只需要一颗健康的卵子
All I need is a healthy ovum
我就可以培育出我的莱纳德·尼莫哀了
and I can grow my own Leonard Nimoy!
好吧  我给你的只是餐巾而已  谢尔顿
Okay, all I'm giving you is the napkin, Sheldon.
我马上回来
Be right back.
给你的  打开吧
Here. Open it.
噢  一份摩托车课程的及格证书
Oh, a gift cerficate for motorcycle lessons.
真会体贴人啊
Very thoughtful.
是啊  而且我查过了
Yeah, and I checked.
第一课就是不会让你再从车上摔下来
Not letting the bike fall on you
而且是车还在原地没动的时候
while standing still is lesson one.
噢  那么  我想你看到我送你的东西  你会很感动的
Oh, then, I think you'll appreciate what I got you.
好的
Okay.
献给孩子们的最酷的101个科学实验
"101 Totally Cool Science Experiments for Kids."
你知道吗  因为你如此迷恋科学
You know, 'cause you're so into science.
谢尔顿  你干了什么啊
Sheldon! What did you do?!
我知道
I know!
这些还不够  对吗
It's not enough, is it?
还有这个
Here.
莱纳德  看哪  谢尔顿在抱我呢
Leonard, look! Sheldon's hugging me.
这是农神节的奇迹啊
It's a Saturnalia miracle.